Guide to the Doris Ulmann Photograph Collection ca. 1910-1934 PR 72
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
  - Necarsulmer, Evelyn (12)
  - Niles, Blair, 1880-1959
  - Niles, John Jacob, 1892-1980, folklorist, musician, Ulmann's assistant (6)
  - Orozco, Jose Clemente, 1883-1949, Mexican painter (2)
  - Page, Arthur Wilson, Editor, World's Work (3)
  - Painter, Henry McMahon, Professor of Clinical Obstetrics, Columbia University (4)
  - Palmer, Walter W., Associate Professor of Medicine, Columbia University (5)
  - Parrish, Anne (3)
  - Peterkin, Julia (2)
  - Phillips, John S., Editor, The American Magazine
  - Powys, Llewelyn, 1884-1939, writer
  - Prudden, T. Mitchell, Emeritus Professor of Pathology, Columbia University
  - Reese, Lizette Woodworth, 1856-1935, poet (3)
  - Roberts, Elizabeth Maddox, 1886-1941, writer (2)
  - Robinson, Boardman, American painter (7)
  - Russell, William Wood, Associate Professor of Clinical Gynecology, Johns Hopkins University (8)
  - Sabin, Florence Rena, Professor of Histology, Johns Hopkins University (8)
  - Sedgwick, Ellery, Editor, Atlantic Monthly 2)
  - Sell, Henry Blackman, editor, Harper's Bazaar (10)
  - Shaw, Albert, Editor, Everybody's magazine
  - Shipman, Louis Evan, Editor, Life(4)
  - Smith, Winford Henry, Superintendent, Johns Hopkins Hospital
  - Smyth, Clifford, Editor, International Book Review
  - Squier, J. Bentley, Professor of Urology, Columbia University (5)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, 1877-1968, dancer
  - Steele, Wilbur Daniel, 1886-1970 (3)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1879-1962
  - Stetten, Dr. DeWitt, 1881-1953, surgeon, Lenox Hill Hospital (3)
  - Strauss, Samuel, Editor, The Villager (2)
  - Thayer, William Sydney, Professor of Medicine, Johns Hopkins University (3)
  - Theobald, Samuel, M.D., Clinical Professor of Ophthalmology, Johns Hopkins University (2)
  - Thomas, Henry M., M.D., Clinical Professor of Neurology, Johns Hopkins University (7)
  - Tilney, Frederic, Professor of Neurology and Neuro-Anatomy, Columbia University (6)
  - Townsend, Reginald T., Editor, Country Life
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1885-1977, American poet
  - Van Doren, Carl, Editor, The Century (13)
  - Van Doren, Margaret (12)
  - Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964, writer, photographer (2)
  - Vance, Arthur T., Editor, Pictorial Review (2)
  - Walpole, Sir Hugh Seymour, 1884-1941, author (2)
  - Walsh, Richard J., Editor, Collier's (17)
  - Weber, Max, Ulmann's art and design teacher at Clarence H. White School of Photography (5)
  - Weed, Lewis Hill, M.D., Professor of Anatomy, Johns Hopkins University
  - Weir, Robert F., Professor of Surgery, Columbia University (2)
  - Welch, William Henry, Director and Head of the Department of Bacteriology and Immunology of School of Hygiene, Johns Hopkins University (6)
  - Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine (17)
  - Wescott, Glenway, writer (2)
  - Whigham, Henry James, Editor, Town and Country (3)
  - White, Clarence H. (2)
  - Whitman, Dr. Royal (2)
  - Widdeman, Margaret (13)
  - Wilder, Thornton (4)
  - Williams, John Whitridge, Professor of Obstetrics and Dean, Johns Hopkins University (9)
  - Wolfe, Thomas, writer (2)
  - Wood, Frances Carter, Director of Cancer Research, Columbia University (2)
  - Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden (15)
  - Yeats, William Butler, poet (2)
  - Young, Hugh Hampton, Clinical Professor of Urology, Johns Hopkins University (2)